{
   
   
    "q1":{
            "question" : "1. which of the following is true about jQuery Selectors?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "jQuery Selectors are used to select one or a group of HTML elements from your web page.",
                "option2" : "jQuery support all the CSS selectors as well as many additional custom selectors.",
                "option3" : "jQuery selectors always start with dollar sign and parentheses: $()",
                "option4" : "all the above"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            },
       
    "q2":{
            "question" : "2. How do you hide an image on a button click using jQuery?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "$('#ImageToHide').hide();",
                "option2" : "$('#ImageToHide').css('visibility','hidden');",
                "option3" : "either of above two",
                "option4" : "$('#ImageToHide').css('display','none');"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            }, 
    
    "q3":{
            "question" : "3. In what scenarios jQuery can be used?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Apply CSS static or dynamic",
                "option2" : "Calling functions on events",
                "option3" : "Mainly for Animation effects",
                "option4" : "all of the above"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            },
    
    "q4":{
            "question" : "4. What is the difference between size and length of jQuery?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Size and length both returns the number of element in an object.",
                "option2" : "Size and length both returns the number of element in an object. But length is faster than the size because length is a property and size is a method.",
                "option3" : "Size and length both returns the number of element in an object. But size is faster than the size because size is a property and length is a method.",
                "option4" : "none"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
    
    "q5":{
            "question" : "5. What are the four parameters used for jQuery Ajax method?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "URL, type, data, catche",
                "option2" : "URL, type, data, filter",
                "option3" : "URL, type, data, key",
                "option4" : "URL, type, data, argument"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            },
    
    "q6":{
            "question" : "6. Which of the following are selectors in jQuery?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "CSS selectors",
                "option2" : "XPath Selector",
                "option3" : "Custom Selector",
                "option4" : "all the above"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            },
     "q7":{
            "question" : "7. Which sign does jQuery use as a shortcut for jQuery?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "the ? Sign",
                "option2" : "the % Sign",
                "option3" : "the $ Sign",
                "option4" : "the # Sign"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            },
       
    "q8":{
            "question" : "8. $('div.intro'). What does it select?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "The first div element with id='intro'",
                "option2" : "The first div element with class='intro'",
                "option3" : "All div elements with id='intro'",
                "option4" : "All div elements with class='intro'"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            }, 
    
    "q9":{
            "question" : "9. Which built-in method returns the index within the calling String object of the first occurrence of the specified value?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "getIndex()",
                "option2" : "location()",
                "option3" : "indexOf",
                "option4" : "none"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            },
    
    "q10":{
            "question" : "10. Which of the following jQuery method checks if event.stopImmediatePropagation() was ever called on this event object?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "isDefaultPrevented()",
                "option2" : "isPropagationStopped()",
                "option3" : "isImmediatePorpagationStopped()",
                "option4" : "None of the above"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            }
}
    
   
   
   
  